<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="action_about_title">About FFUpdater</string>
    <string name="action_settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="app_description">Updater for privacy friendly browsers</string>
    <string name="app_icon">app icon</string>
    <string name="app_name">FFUpdater</string>
    <string name="application_installation_was_not_successful">Application installation was not successful</string>
    <string name="application_successfully_installed">Application successfully installed</string>
    <string name="available_version">Available: %1$s</string>
    <string name="available_version_error">"<u>ERROR</u>"</string>
    <string name="available_version_loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="background_job_failure__notification_text">Please report this error. Click to view the error report.</string>
    <string name="background_job_failure__notification_title">Background update check failed</string>
    <string name="brave__description">Privately browse the internet, for free! The Brave Private Browser App is your fast, free, and safe private web browser with ad blocker and pop-up blocker. Privately browse and search the internet without being tracked by advertisers, malware and pop-ups.</string>
    <string name="brave__title">Brave Private Browser</string>
    <string name="brave__warning">Brave uses the technical foundation of the Google Chrome (Chromium) - some people don\'t like this. Do you want to install Brave?</string>
    <string name="brave_beta__description">Welcome to Brave Beta for Android!\nTry out the newest features and give early feedback: https://brave.com/msupport\nYou can install Brave Beta alongside your current version of Brave for Android.</string>
    <string name="brave_beta__title">Brave Browser (Beta)</string>
    <string name="brave_nightly__description">Welcome to Brave Nightly (Developer) for Android!\nTry out the newest features and give early feedback: https://brave.com/msupport\nYou can install Brave Nightly alongside your current version of Brave for Android.</string>
    <string name="brave_nightly__title">Brave Browser (Nightly)</string>
    <string name="bromite__description">Bromite aims at providing a no-clutter browsing experience without privacy-invasive features and with the addition of a fast ad-blocking engine. Minimal UI changes are applied to help curbing the idea of "browser as an advertisement platform".</string>
    <string name="bromite__title">Bromite</string>
    <string name="bromite__warning">Bromite uses the technical foundation of the Google Chrome (Chromium) - some people don\'t like this. Do you want to install Bromite?</string>
    <string name="bromite_systemwebview__description">The SystemWebView package contains the core browser/rendering engine of Bromite and its same features; it offers the possibility to replace the default browser component for the whole Android system.</string>
    <string name="bromite_systemwebview__title">Bromite SystemWebView</string>
    <string name="but_was">But was:</string>
    <string name="crash_report__copy_crash_report_to_clipboard">Copy crash report to clipboard</string>
    <string name="crash_report__explain_text__install_activity_fetching_url">The following error occurred when the download URL was fetched. If this error occurs frequently, feel free to report it on notabug.org, GitHub or GitLab. Please don\'t forget to add your crash report from the clipboard and the description of how you reproduce this error.</string>
    <string name="crash_report__explain_text__main_activity_update_check">The following error occurred when checking for updates in the main view. If this error occurs frequently, feel free to report it on notabug.org, GitHub or GitLab. Please don\'t forget to add your crash report from the clipboard and the description of how you reproduce this error.</string>
    <string name="crash_report__explain_text__uncaught_throwable">Unfortunately, FFUpdater has crashed. Please report this error on notabug.org, GitHub or GitLab. Add to your issue the crash report from the clipboard and a description on how to reproduce the bug.</string>
    <string name="crash_report__go_to_github">Go to GitHub</string>
    <string name="crash_report__go_to_gitlab">Go to GitLab</string>
    <string name="crash_report__got_to_notabug_org">Go to notabug.org</string>
    <string name="default_theme_preference" translatable="false">3</string>
    <string name="device_too_old_dialog__message">The application requires Android %1$s. But your device is only running Android %2$s. Either choose a different app, update your operating system or switch to a newer smartphone.</string>
    <string name="device_too_old_dialog__title">Device is too old</string>
    <string name="dialog_button__do_not_install">No, don\'t install it</string>
    <string name="dialog_button__yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="download_notification__channel_description">Shows when app updates are downloaded in the background.</string>
    <string name="download_notification__channel_name">Notification about downloads in the background</string>
    <string name="download_notification__message">Currently downloading updates for installed apps in the background.</string>
    <string name="download_notification__title">Downloading app updates</string>
    <string name="download_the_app">download the app</string>
    <string name="error_notification__channel_description">Show errors of the background update checker</string>
    <string name="error_notification__channel_name">Background errors</string>
    <string name="failed_update_notification__channel_description">Notification channel for failed %1$s updates.</string>
    <string name="failed_update_notification__channel_name">%1$s update failure notification</string>
    <string name="failed_update_notification__notification_message">Error (%1$d): %2$s</string>
    <string name="failed_update_notification__notification_title">%1$s could not be updated.</string>
    <string name="firefox_beta__description">Firefox Browser for Android is automatically private and incredibly fast. Thousands of online trackers are following you every day, collecting information about where you go online and slowing down your speed. Firefox blocks over 2000 of these trackers by default and there are ad blocker add-ons available if you want to customize your browser even more. With Firefox, you’ll get the security you deserve and the speed you need in a private, mobile browser.</string>
    <string name="firefox_beta__title">Firefox for Android Beta</string>
    <string name="firefox_beta__warning">This app is designed for developers and testers. It may contain various bugs that can affect your usual work with the browser. Do you want to install it?</string>
    <string name="firefox_focus__description">This is a modification of the Firefox browser aimed to increase privacy.</string>
    <string name="firefox_focus__title">Firefox Focus</string>
    <string name="firefox_klar__description">Firefox Klar is developed for Germany, Austria and Switzerland, but can be used by users in any country. It is very similar to Firefox Focus, but the name was changed in German-speaking countries to avoid confusion with the magazine Focus by Hubert Burda Media group. Unlike Firefox Focus, Firefox Klar has telemetry disabled by default due to strict German privacy laws.</string>
    <string name="firefox_klar__title">Firefox Klar</string>
    <string name="firefox_nightly__description">Please note that this app used to be titled Firefox Preview. It has now been transitioned to Firefox Nightly. \n\nFirefox Nightly is a developmental channel for new Mozilla Firefox releases. \n\nFirefox Nightly is designed to showcase the more experimental builds of Firefox. The Nightly channel allows users to experience the newest Firefox innovations in an unstable environment and provide feedback on features and performance to help determine what makes the final release.</string>
    <string name="firefox_nightly__title">Firefox Nightly</string>
    <string name="firefox_nightly__warning">This app is designed for developers and testers. It may contain various bugs that can affect your usual work with the browser. Do you want to install it?</string>
    <string name="firefox_release__description">Firefox Browser for Android is automatically private and incredibly fast. Thousands of online trackers are following you every day, collecting information about where you go online and slowing down your speed. Firefox blocks over 2000 of these trackers by default and there are ad blocker add-ons available if you want to customize your browser even more. With Firefox, you’ll get the security you deserve and the speed you need in a private, mobile browser.</string>
    <string name="firefox_release__title">Firefox Browser</string>
    <string name="github" translatable="false">GitHub</string>
    <string name="go_back">Go back</string>
    <string name="iceraven__description">Definitely not brought to you by Mozilla! \n\nIceraven Browser is a web browser for Android, based on Mozilla\'s Fenix version of Firefox, GeckoView and Mozilla Android Components. \n\nOur goal is to be a close fork of the new Firefox for Android that seeks to provide users with more options, more opportunities to customize (including a broad extension library), and more information about the pages they visit and how their browsers are interacting with those pages.</string>
    <string name="iceraven__title">Iceraven Browser</string>
    <string name="infobox">This is an updater for multiple browsers from Mozilla. Click the plus-button for installation and the down-arrow-button for updating. You can check for new updates by down-swiping or reopening the app. By default the app will check regularly for updates in the background. I did my best to secure the installation/updating process - feel free to double-check it or improve it by creating a pull-request. \n\nLast successful background update check: %1$s</string>
    <string name="information_about_the_app">information about the app</string>
    <string name="install_activity__delete_cache_button_text">clear cache</string>
    <string name="install_activity__delete_cache_explanation">If you think that FFUpdater has cached a faulty app update, click the \"clear cache\" button to delete the cache for this app.</string>
    <string name="install_activity__download_app_with_status">Download application (%1$s)</string>
    <string name="install_activity__download_failed">Download failed</string>
    <string name="install_activity__downloaded_application_from">Downloaded application from:</string>
    <string name="install_activity__downloaded_application_is_not_verified">Downloaded application is NOT verified</string>
    <string name="install_activity__downloaded_application_is_verified">Downloaded application is verified</string>
    <string name="install_activity__exception__show_button">"<u>Show the detailed error report.</u>"</string>
    <string name="install_activity__expected_sha_256_certificate_fingerprint">Expected SHA-256 certificate fingerprint:</string>
    <string name="install_activity__external_storage_not_accessible">External storage is not available - can\'t start download. Current status is:</string>
    <string name="install_activity__fetch_url_for_download">Fetch download URL from %1$s</string>
    <string name="install_activity__fetched_url_for_download_successfully">Fetched download URL from %1$s</string>
    <string name="install_activity__github_rate_limit_exceeded">GitHub-API rate limit is exceeded. Please try the download again in the next hour.</string>
    <string name="install_activity__invalid_downloaded_certificate_fingerprint_explanation">Either an attacker has replaced the correct download with a tampered one or the certificate checker doesn\'t work anymore. You can double-check the certificate fingerprint on apkmirror.com or you can create an issue on https://notabug.org/Tobiwan/ffupdater to inform my about the bug.</string>
    <string name="install_activity__invalid_installed_certificate_fingerprint_explanation">Either a tampered application has been installed or the certificate checker doesn\'t work anymore. You can double-check the certificate fingerprint on apkmirror.com or you can create an issue on https://notabug.org/Tobiwan/ffupdater to inform my about the bug. \n\nI recommend you to uninstall the application.</string>
    <string name="install_activity__open_cache_explanation">You can open the cache folder to copy the APK file to a place with more free storage.</string>
    <string name="install_activity__open_cache_folder_button_text">open cache folder</string>
    <string name="install_activity__retrigger_installation__button_title">Retry App Installation</string>
    <string name="install_activity__sha_256_certificate_fingerprint">SHA-256 certificate fingerprint:</string>
    <string name="install_activity__temporary_network_issue">A temporary network issue occurred. Please retry later.</string>
    <string name="install_activity__too_low_memory_description">Your device is low on storage (only %1$d MB free). This will lead to download or installation failure.</string>
    <string name="install_activity__too_low_memory_title">Low Disk Space</string>
    <string name="install_activity__try_disable_miui_optimization">If you are using Xiaomi or MIUI, try disabling \"MIUI Optimization\".</string>
    <string name="install_activity__unknown_signature_of_installed_app_text1">You have to uninstall the existing app before FFUpdater can install or update the app. Backup your data because the uninstall will delete all your bookmarks, settings etc.</string>
    <string name="install_activity__unknown_signature_of_installed_app_text2">Reason: The current installed app is not signed by the original developer - maybe it\'s signed by F-Droid. Android refuses to update an app if different people signed the installed and the updated version.</string>
    <string name="install_activity__use_cached_downloaded_apk">Use already downloaded file from:</string>
    <string name="install_activity__verifying_downloaded_application_certificate">Verifying application certificate</string>
    <string name="install_activity__you_can_now_close_this_window">You can now close this window</string>
    <string name="install_activity_label">Install Application</string>
    <string name="install_app">Install app</string>
    <string name="install_new_app">Install new app</string>
    <string name="install_same_version_dialog__message">The latest version of this app is already installed. Do you want to download and install the latest version again?</string>
    <string name="install_same_version_dialog__title">Same version installed</string>
    <string name="installed_app_is_not_verified">Installed app is NOT verified</string>
    <string name="installed_application_is_verified">Installed application is verified</string>
    <string name="installed_version">Installed: %1$s</string>
    <string name="lockwise__description">PASSWORD ACCESS FOR YOU, &amp; ONLY YOU \n\nSecurely track your Firefox passwords &amp; access them anywhere. Quickly open any website from the app to get into your accounts</string>
    <string name="lockwise__title">Firefox Lockwise</string>
    <string name="main_activity__github_api_limit_exceeded">"<u>GitHub-API limit exceeded. Retry next hour.</u>"</string>
    <string name="main_activity__no_unmetered_network">No unmetered network</string>
    <string name="main_activity__subtitle">Update your browsers from Mozilla</string>
    <string name="main_activity__temporary_network_issue">"<u>Temporary network issue. Retry later.</u>"</string>
    <string name="manage_storage_activity__delete_button">Delete cached app updates.</string>
    <string name="manage_storage_activity__explanation">FFUpdater caches already downloaded app updates and stores them in the \'Android/data/de.marmaro.krt.ffupdater/files/Download\' folder.\n\nThis saves bandwidth when an app is not successfully installed or updated. Also, the cache is needed so that updates that were downloaded in the background can be installed later.\n\nIf you decide to delete these app updates, you may have to download them again.</string>
    <string name="mozilla_ci" translatable="false">Mozilla CI</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="request_installation_permission_dialog__abort">Abort</string>
    <string name="request_installation_permission_dialog__grant_permission">Grant permission</string>
    <string name="request_installation_permission_dialog__message">FFUpdater is missing the permission to install and update apps. You have to grant these permissions or FFUpdater will not work.</string>
    <string name="request_installation_permission_dialog__title">Installer permission</string>
    <string name="running_downloads_dialog__message">The app is downloading updates in the background now. Do you want to start a new download that may take longer?</string>
    <string name="running_downloads_dialog__negative">No, don\'t download it</string>
    <string name="running_downloads_dialog__title">Running downloads</string>
    <string name="running_downloads_dialog__yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="session_installer__not_enough_storage">The operation failed because not enough storage is available: %1$s</string>
    <string name="session_installer__status_failure">The operation failed in a generic way. The system will always try to provide a more specific failure reason, but in some rare cases this may be delivered.</string>
    <string name="session_installer__status_failure_aborted">The operation failed because it was actively aborted. For example, the user actively declined requested permissions, or the session was abandoned.</string>
    <string name="session_installer__status_failure_blocked">The operation failed because it was blocked. For example, a device policy may be blocking the operation, a package verifier may have blocked the operation, or the app may be required for core system operation.</string>
    <string name="session_installer__status_failure_conflict">The operation failed because it conflicts (or is inconsistent with) with another package already installed on the device. For example, an existing permission, incompatible certificates, etc. The user may be able to uninstall another app to fix the issue.</string>
    <string name="session_installer__status_failure_incompatible">The operation failed because it is fundamentally incompatible with this device. For example, the app may require a hardware feature that doesn\'t exist, it may be missing native code for the ABIs supported by the device, or it requires a newer SDK version, etc.</string>
    <string name="session_installer__status_failure_invalid">The operation failed because one or more of the APKs was invalid. For example, they might be malformed, corrupt, incorrectly signed, mismatched, etc.</string>
    <string name="session_installer__status_failure_storage">The operation failed because of storage issues. For example, the device may be running low on space, or external media may be unavailable. The user may be able to help free space or insert different external media.</string>
    <string name="settings__activity_label">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings__background__download__enabled__summary">When an update is detected, download it. This will later speed up the update process.</string>
    <string name="settings__background__download__enabled__title">Download app updates</string>
    <string name="settings__background__download__metered__summary">Not recommended for users with limited mobile data.</string>
    <string name="settings__background__download__metered__title">Download app updates on metered networks</string>
    <string name="settings__background__installation__enabled__summary">Try to install updates without user interaction.</string>
    <string name="settings__background__installation__enabled__title">Install update</string>
    <string name="settings__background__update_check__enabled__summary">Check for new updates at regular intervals.</string>
    <string name="settings__background__update_check__enabled__title">Update check</string>
    <string name="settings__background__update_check__excluded_apps__summary">Useful if you don\'t want to update an app and don\'t want to receive update notifications for it.</string>
    <string name="settings__background__update_check__excluded_apps__title">Exclude apps from update check</string>
    <string name="settings__background__update_check__interval__title">Update check interval</string>
    <string name="settings__background__update_check__metered__title">Update checks on metered networks</string>
    <string name="settings__background_category__summary">Settings when the app is working in the background and is invisible to the user.</string>
    <string name="settings__background_category__title">Background</string>
    <string name="settings__foreground__download__metered__summary">Useful for users with limited mobile data.</string>
    <string name="settings__foreground__download__metered__title">Download updates on metered networks</string>
    <string name="settings__foreground__theme_preference__summary">Choose between light and dark theme</string>
    <string name="settings__foreground__theme_preference__title">Choose theme</string>
    <string name="settings__foreground__update_check__metered__summary">Allow update checks on metered networks such as mobile data.</string>
    <string name="settings__foreground__update_check__metered__title">Update checks on metered networks</string>
    <string name="settings__foreground_category__summary">Settings when the user interface is visible.</string>
    <string name="settings__foreground_category__title">Foreground</string>
    <string name="settings__theme_battery_saver">Dark when Battery Saver active</string>
    <string name="settings__theme_dark">Dark</string>
    <string name="settings__theme_light">Light</string>
    <string name="settings__theme_system_default">Use system default</string>
    <string name="show_warning_before_installation_dialog__title">Warning</string>
    <string name="successful_update__notification_message">App has been successfully updated in the background.</string>
    <string name="successful_update_notification__channel_description">Notification channel for successful %1$s updates.</string>
    <string name="successful_update_notification__channel_name">%1$s successful update notification</string>
    <string name="successful_update_notification__notification_title">%1$s has been updated.</string>
    <string name="ungoogled_chromium__description">Google Chromium, sans integration with Google.\n\nWithout signing in to a Google Account, Chromium does pretty well in terms of security and privacy. However, Chromium still has some dependency on Google web services and binaries. In addition, Google designed Chromium to be easy and intuitive for users, which means they compromise on transparency and control of internal operations.</string>
    <string name="ungoogled_chromium__title">Ungoogled Chromium</string>
    <string name="ungoogled_chromium__warning">Ungoogled Chromium uses the technical foundation of the Google Chrome (Chromium) - some people don\'t like this. Do you want to install Ungoogled Chromium?</string>
    <string name="unsupported_abi_dialog__message">The selected browser is incompatible with your smartphone\'s processor. Please select a different browser.</string>
    <string name="unsupported_abi_dialog__title">Unsupported device</string>
    <string name="update_interval__12h">12 hours</string>
    <string name="update_interval__15min">15 minutes</string>
    <string name="update_interval__18h">18 hours</string>
    <string name="update_interval__1d">1 day</string>
    <string name="update_interval__1h">1 hour</string>
    <string name="update_interval__1m">1 month</string>
    <string name="update_interval__1w">1 week</string>
    <string name="update_interval__2d">2 days</string>
    <string name="update_interval__2h">2 hours</string>
    <string name="update_interval__2w">2 weeks</string>
    <string name="update_interval__30min">30 minutes</string>
    <string name="update_interval__3d">3 days</string>
    <string name="update_interval__4d">4 days</string>
    <string name="update_interval__4h">4 hours</string>
    <string name="update_interval__5d">5 days</string>
    <string name="update_interval__6d">6 days</string>
    <string name="update_interval__6h">6 hours</string>
    <string name="update_interval__8h">8 hours</string>
    <string name="update_notification__channel_description">Notification channel for available %1$s updates.</string>
    <string name="update_notification__channel_name">"%1$s" update notification</string>
    <string name="update_notification__text">Click to install update</string>
    <string name="update_notification__title">Update for "%1$s" available</string>
    <string name="vivaldi__description">Discover a blazingly fast Internet browser! Vivaldi is a new, free, and private web browser built with flexibility in mind. It comes packed with useful features including a built-in AdBlocker (pop-up blocker), tracking protection, and private translation. Browser options like proper desktop-style tabs, dark/light Themes, and layout choices help you make it yours.</string>
    <string name="vivaldi__source" translatable="false">https://vivaldi.com/download/</string>
    <string name="vivaldi__title">Vivaldi Browser</string>
    <string name="vivaldi__warning">Vivaldi is only partially open source (see <a href="https://vivaldi.com/blog/vivaldi-browser-open-source/">https://vivaldi.com/blog/vivaldi-browser-open-source/</a> for more info). It also uses the technical foundation of the Google Chrome (Chromium).\n\nSome people don\'t like this. Do you want to install Vivaldi?</string>
    <string name="general__use_root__summary">FFUpdater will ask for root permission if this option is enabled and an app is installed or updated. To gain root privileges, you must use Magisk or other tools. If enabled, FFUpdater will install or updates apps in the foreground and background without user interaction.</string>
    <string name="general__use_root__title">Use root permission to install or update apps</string>
</resources>
