<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="action_about_title">About FFUpdater</string>
    <string name="app_card__app_warning_button_description">Show warnings about this app</string>
    <string name="app_description">Updater for privacy friendly browsers</string>
    <string name="app_icon">app icon</string>
    <string name="app_name">FFUpdater</string>
    <string name="app_warning_dialog__title">Warning</string>
    <string name="application_installation_was_not_successful">Application installation was not successful</string>
    <string name="application_successfully_installed">Application successfully installed</string>
    <string name="available_version">Available: %1$s</string>
    <string name="notification__error__text">Please report this error. Click to view the error report.</string>
    <string name="notification__error__title">Background update check failed</string>
    <string name="brave__description">Privately browse the internet, for free! The Brave Private Browser App is your fast, free, and safe private web browser with ad blocker and pop-up blocker. Privately browse and search the internet without being tracked by advertisers, malware and pop-ups.</string>
    <string name="brave__title">Brave Private Browser</string>
    <string name="brave__warning">- Brave uses the technical foundation of Google Chrome and thus indirectly supports the monopoly position of the Chromium render engine.\n- Due to its Basic Attention Token BAT on the Ethereum blockchain the project has ties with cryptocurrency. Blockchains have many problems and should be avoided in my view.</string>
    <string name="brave_beta__description">Welcome to Brave Beta for Android!\nTry out the newest features and give early feedback: https://brave.com/msupport\nYou can install Brave Beta alongside your current version of Brave for Android.</string>
    <string name="brave_beta__title">Brave Browser (Beta)</string>
    <string name="brave_nightly__description">Welcome to Brave Nightly (Developer) for Android!\nTry out the newest features and give early feedback: https://brave.com/msupport\nYou can install Brave Nightly alongside your current version of Brave for Android.</string>
    <string name="brave_nightly__title">Brave Browser (Nightly)</string>
    <string name="bromite__description">Bromite aims at providing a no-clutter browsing experience without privacy-invasive features and with the addition of a fast ad-blocking engine. Minimal UI changes are applied to help curbing the idea of "browser as an advertisement platform".</string>
    <string name="bromite__title">Bromite</string>
    <string name="bromite__warning">- Bromite uses the technical foundation of Google Chrome and thus indirectly supports the monopoly position of the Chromium render engine.</string>
    <string name="bromite_systemwebview__description">The SystemWebView package contains the core browser/rendering engine of Bromite and its same features. It offers the possibility to replace the default browser component for the whole Android system.</string>
    <string name="bromite_systemwebview__title">Bromite SystemWebView</string>
    <string name="crash_report__copy_crash_report_to_clipboard">Copy crash report to clipboard</string>
    <string name="install_activity__download_file_failed__crash_text">The following error occurred during download. If this error occurs frequently, feel free to submit the crash report to notabug.org, GitHub or GitLab.</string>
    <string name="crash_report__explain_text__download_activity_fetching_url">This error occurred when the download metadata was fetched. If this error occurs frequently, feel free to submit the crash report to notabug.org, GitHub or GitLab.</string>
    <string name="crash_report__explain_text__download_activity_install_file">This error occurred during installation. If this error occurs frequently, feel free to submit the crash report to notabug.org, GitHub or GitLab.</string>
    <string name="crash_report__explain_text__download_activity_update_check">This error occurred when checking for updates in the main view. If this error occurs frequently, feel free to submit the crash report to notabug.org, GitHub or GitLab.</string>
    <string name="crash_report__explain_text__uncaught_throwable">Unfortunately, FFUpdater crashed last time and logged this error. Please submit the crash report to notabug.org, GitHub or GitLab.</string>
    <string name="crash_report__go_to_github">Go to GitHub</string>
    <string name="crash_report__go_to_gitlab">Go to GitLab</string>
    <string name="crash_report__got_to_notabug_org">Go to notabug.org</string>
    <string name="default_theme_preference" translatable="false">3</string>
    <string name="dialog_button__do_not_install">No, don\'t install it</string>
    <string name="dialog_button__yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="notification__download_error__channel_descr">Shows when update downloads in the background fail.</string>
    <string name="notification__download_error__channel_name">Notification about download errors in the background</string>
    <string name="notification__download_error__descr">The background download of the %1$s update failed. If this error occurs frequently, feel free to report it on notabug.org, GitHub or GitLab.</string>
    <string name="notification__download_error__text">The background download of the %1$s update failed. If this error occurs frequently, click here to view the error report.</string>
    <string name="notification__download_error__title">Background download of update failed</string>
    <string name="notification__download_running__channel_descr">Shows when app updates are downloaded in the background.</string>
    <string name="notification__download_running__channel_name">Notification about downloads in the background</string>
    <string name="notification__download_running__title">Downloading app updates</string>
    <string name="app_card__download_the_app">download the app</string>
    <string name="notification__eol_apps__channel_description">Notification channel for warnings about outdated apps.</string>
    <string name="notification__eol_apps__channel_name">Outdated apps notification</string>
    <string name="notification__eol_apps__text">You have outdated apps which should not be used anymore. Click for more information.</string>
    <string name="notification__eol_apps__title">Outdated apps installed</string>
    <string name="notification__error__channel_descr">Show errors of the background update checker</string>
    <string name="notification__error__channel_name">Background errors</string>
    <string name="firefox_beta__description">Firefox Browser for Android is automatically private and incredibly fast. Thousands of online trackers are following you every day, collecting information about where you go online and slowing down your speed. Firefox blocks over 2000 of these trackers by default and there are ad blocker add-ons available if you want to customize your browser even more. With Firefox, you’ll get the security you deserve and the speed you need in a private, mobile browser.</string>
    <string name="firefox_beta__title">Firefox for Android Beta</string>
    <string name="firefox_beta__warning">- This app is designed for developers and testers. It may contain various bugs that can affect your usual work with the browser.</string>
    <string name="firefox_focus__description">This is a modification of the Firefox browser aimed to increase privacy.</string>
    <string name="firefox_focus__title">Firefox Focus</string>
    <string name="firefox_klar__description">Firefox Klar is developed for Germany, Austria and Switzerland, but can be used by users in any country. It is very similar to Firefox Focus, but the name was changed in German-speaking countries to avoid confusion with the magazine Focus by Hubert Burda Media group. Unlike Firefox Focus, Firefox Klar has telemetry disabled by default due to strict German privacy laws.</string>
    <string name="firefox_klar__title">Firefox Klar</string>
    <string name="firefox_nightly__description">Please note that this app used to be titled Firefox Preview. It has now been transitioned to Firefox Nightly. \n\nFirefox Nightly is a developmental channel for new Mozilla Firefox releases. \n\nFirefox Nightly is designed to showcase the more experimental builds of Firefox. The Nightly channel allows users to experience the newest Firefox innovations in an unstable environment and provide feedback on features and performance to help determine what makes the final release.</string>
    <string name="firefox_nightly__title">Firefox Nightly</string>
    <string name="firefox_release__description">Firefox Browser for Android is automatically private and incredibly fast. Thousands of online trackers are following you every day, collecting information about where you go online and slowing down your speed. Firefox blocks over 2000 of these trackers by default and there are ad blocker add-ons available if you want to customize your browser even more. With Firefox, you’ll get the security you deserve and the speed you need in a private, mobile browser.</string>
    <string name="firefox_release__title">Firefox Browser</string>
    <string name="firefox_release__warning">- An improved version of Firefox is also available on F-Droid under the name "Fennec F-Droid".</string>
    <string name="iceraven__description">Definitely not brought to you by Mozilla! \n\nIceraven Browser is a web browser for Android, based on Mozilla\'s Fenix version of Firefox, GeckoView and Mozilla Android Components. \n\nOur goal is to be a close fork of the new Firefox for Android that seeks to provide users with more options, more opportunities to customize (including a broad extension library), and more information about the pages they visit and how their browsers are interacting with those pages.</string>
    <string name="iceraven__title">Iceraven Browser</string>
    <string name="iceraven__warning">- The maintainer gives no warranties or guarantees of security or updates or even stability.\n - The project takes longer than usual to provide security updates.</string>
    <string name="infobox">This is an updater for privacy-friendly browsers. Click the plus button to install new apps. Swipe down to force a check for new updates. By default, the app will periodically check for updates in the background, which will then be downloaded and eventually installed. Click the gear to customize the behavior in the settings.
\n
\nLast successful background update check: %1$s</string>
    <string name="app_card__information_about_the_app">Information about the app</string>
    <string name="download_activity__delete_cache_button_text">clear cache</string>
    <string name="download_activity__delete_cache_explanation">If you think that FFUpdater has cached a faulty app update or if you want to save space, click the button to delete the downloaded file.</string>
    <string name="download_activity__different_installer_info__text">If the installation fails frequently, try switching to the \'native installer\' in the settings.</string>
    <string name="download_activity__download_app_with_status">Downloading application</string>
    <string name="download_activity__download_failed">Download failed</string>
    <string name="download_activity__downloaded_application_from">Downloaded application from:</string>
    <string name="app_installer__signature_of_download_is_invalid">Downloaded application is NOT verified</string>
    <string name="download_activity__exception__show_button">"<u>Show the detailed error report.</u>"</string>
    <string name="download_activity__external_storage_not_accessible">External storage is not available - can\'t start download. Current status is:</string>
    <string name="download_activity__fetch_url_for_download">Fetch metadata from %1$s</string>
    <string name="download_activity__fetched_url_for_download_successfully">Fetched metadata from %1$s</string>
    <string name="download_activity__file_uri_exposed_toast">Can\'t expose file path to other apps. Please open the folder yourself with your preferred file manager."</string>
    <string name="download_activity__github_rate_limit_exceeded">GitHub-API rate limit is exceeded. Please try the download again in the next hour.</string>
    <string name="download_activity__open_cache_explanation">You can open the cache folder to copy the APK file to a place with more free storage. Unfortunately, on Android 11+ only few file managers can access this folder within Android/data.</string>
    <string name="download_activity__open_cache_folder_button_text">open cache folder</string>
    <string name="download_activity__open_folder">Open folder</string>
    <string name="download_activity__sha_256_certificate_fingerprint">SHA-256 certificate fingerprint:</string>
    <string name="download_activity__temporary_network_issue">A temporary network issue occurred. Please retry later.</string>
    <string name="download_activity__too_low_memory_description">Your device is low on storage (only %1$d MB free). This will lead to download or installation failure.</string>
    <string name="download_activity__too_low_memory_title">Low Disk Space</string>
    <string name="download_activity__use_cached_downloaded_apk">Use already downloaded file from:</string>
    <string name="download_activity__you_can_now_close_this_window">You can now close this window</string>
    <string name="download_activity__label">Download Application</string>
    <string name="install_new_app">Install new app</string>
    <string name="install_same_version_dialog__message">The latest version of this app is already installed. Do you want to download and install the latest version again?</string>
    <string name="install_same_version_dialog__title">Same version installed</string>
    <string name="notification__install_error__channel_descr">Notification channel for failed %1$s updates.</string>
    <string name="notification__install_error__channel_name">%1$s update failure notification</string>
    <string name="notification__install_error__text">Error (%1$d): %2$s</string>
    <string name="notification__install_error__title">%1$s could not be updated</string>
    <string name="notification__install_success__channel_descr">Notification channel for successful %1$s updates.</string>
    <string name="notification__install_success__channel_name">%1$s successful update notification</string>
    <string name="notification__install_success__text">App has been updated in the background.</string>
    <string name="notification__install_success__title">%1$s has been updated</string>
    <string name="app_installer__installed_app_has_invalid_signature">Installed app is NOT verified</string>
    <string name="installed_application_is_verified">Installed application is verified</string>
    <string name="installed_version">Installed: %1$s</string>
    <string name="kiwi__description">Kiwi Browser is made to browse the internet, read news, watch videos and listen to music, without annoyances.</string>
    <string name="kiwi__title">Kiwi Browser Next</string>
    <string name="kiwi__warning">- Kiwi uses the technical foundation of Google Chrome and thus indirectly supports the monopoly position of the Chromium render engine.
\n- Kiwi is not an ideal privacy browser but has a good addon support.
\n- The browser is getting paid by search engines for every search done using Kiwi Browser. Depending on the search engine choice, requests may go via Kiwibrowser / Kiwisearchservices servers.
\n- Google Ads in Kiwi may use the location data for ads - but you can disable it by disabling the Discovery feature. But this will soon change. See https://privacy.kiwibrowser.org/ for more details.</string>
    <string name="lockwise__description">PASSWORD ACCESS FOR YOU, &amp; ONLY YOU
\n
\nSecurely track your Firefox passwords &amp; access them anywhere. Quickly open any website from the app to get into your accounts.</string>
    <string name="lockwise__eol_reason">Mozilla dropped the support in December 2021. Please switch to another password safe.</string>
    <string name="lockwise__title">Firefox Lockwise</string>
    <string name="main_activity__github_api_limit_exceeded">"<u>GitHub-API limit exceeded. Retry next hour.</u>"</string>
    <string name="main_activity__no_unmetered_network">No unmetered network</string>
    <string name="main_activity__subtitle">Updater for privacy friendly browsers</string>
    <string name="main_activity__temporary_network_issue">"<u>Temporary network issue. Retry later.</u>"</string>
    <string name="main_activity__an_error_occurred">"<u>An error occurred. Retry later.</u>"</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="request_installation_permission_dialog__abort">Abort</string>
    <string name="request_installation_permission_dialog__grant_permission">Grant permission</string>
    <string name="request_installation_permission_dialog__message">FFUpdater is missing the permission to install and update apps. You have to grant these permissions or FFUpdater will not work.</string>
    <string name="request_installation_permission_dialog__title">Installer permission</string>
    <string name="running_downloads_dialog__message">The app is downloading updates in the background now. Do you want to start a new download that may take longer?</string>
    <string name="running_downloads_dialog__negative">No, don\'t download it</string>
    <string name="running_downloads_dialog__title">Running downloads</string>
    <string name="running_downloads_dialog__yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="session_installer__require_user_interaction">Require user interaction. You must first update the app via the FFUpdater user interface. Only then are silent background updates for the respective app allowed.</string>
    <string name="session_installer__status_failure">The operation failed in a generic way. The system will always try to provide a more specific failure reason, but in some rare cases this may be delivered.</string>
    <string name="session_installer__status_failure_aborted">The operation failed because it was actively aborted. For example, the user actively declined requested permissions, or the session was abandoned.</string>
    <string name="session_installer__status_failure_blocked">The operation failed because it was blocked. For example, a device policy may be blocking the operation, a package verifier may have blocked the operation, or the app may be required for core system operation.</string>
    <string name="session_installer__status_failure_conflict">The operation failed because it conflicts (or is inconsistent with) with another package already installed on the device. For example, an existing permission, incompatible certificates, etc. The user may be able to uninstall another app to fix the issue.</string>
    <string name="session_installer__status_failure_incompatible">The operation failed because it is fundamentally incompatible with this device. For example, the app may require a hardware feature that doesn\'t exist, it may be missing native code for the ABIs supported by the device, or it requires a newer SDK version, etc.</string>
    <string name="session_installer__status_failure_invalid">The operation failed because one or more of the APKs was invalid. For example, they might be malformed, corrupt, incorrectly signed, mismatched, etc.</string>
    <string name="session_installer__status_failure_storage">The operation failed because of storage issues. For example, the device may be running low on space, or external media may be unavailable. The user may be able to help free space or insert different external media.</string>
    <string name="settings_activity__label">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings__b_f__delete_cache_if_install_failed">Delete the downloaded update if the installation fails.</string>
    <string name="settings__b_f__delete_cache_if_install_successful">Delete the downloaded update if the installation is successful.</string>
    <string name="settings__background__download__enabled__summary">When an update is detected, download it. This will later speed up the update process.</string>
    <string name="settings__background__download__enabled__title">Download app updates</string>
    <string name="settings__background__download__metered__summary">Not recommended for users with limited mobile data.</string>
    <string name="settings__background__download__metered__title">Download app updates on metered networks</string>
    <string name="settings__background__installation__enabled__summary">Try to install updates without user interaction.</string>
    <string name="settings__background__installation__enabled__title">Install update</string>
    <string name="settings__background__update_check__enabled__summary">Check for new updates at regular intervals.</string>
    <string name="settings__background__update_check__enabled__title">Update check</string>
    <string name="settings__background__update_check__excluded_apps__summary">Useful if you don\'t want to update an app and don\'t want to receive update notifications for it.</string>
    <string name="settings__background__update_check__excluded_apps__title">Exclude apps from update check</string>
    <string name="settings__background__update_check__interval__title">Update check interval</string>
    <string name="settings__background__update_check__metered__title">Update checks on metered networks</string>
    <string name="settings__background_category__summary">Settings when the app is working in the background and is invisible to the user.</string>
    <string name="settings__background_category__title">Background</string>
    <string name="settings__foreground__download__metered__title">Download updates on metered networks</string>
    <string name="settings__foreground__hide_warning_buttons">Hide the warning button for installed app.</string>
    <string name="settings__foreground__theme_preference__summary">Choose between light and dark theme</string>
    <string name="settings__foreground__theme_preference__title">Choose theme</string>
    <string name="settings__foreground__update_check__metered__summary">Allow update checks on metered networks such as mobile data.</string>
    <string name="settings__foreground__update_check__metered__title">Update checks on metered networks</string>
    <string name="settings__foreground_category__summary">Settings when the user interface is visible.</string>
    <string name="settings__foreground_category__title">Foreground</string>
    <string name="settings__installer_category__title">Installer</string>
    <string name="settings__theme_battery_saver">Dark when Battery Saver active</string>
    <string name="settings__theme_dark">Dark</string>
    <string name="settings__theme_light">Light</string>
    <string name="settings__theme_system_default">Use system default</string>
    <string name="ungoogled_chromium__description">Google Chromium, sans integration with Google.\n\nWithout signing in to a Google Account, Chromium does pretty well in terms of security and privacy. However, Chromium still has some dependency on Google web services and binaries. In addition, Google designed Chromium to be easy and intuitive for users, which means they compromise on transparency and control of internal operations.</string>
    <string name="ungoogled_chromium__title">Ungoogled Chromium</string>
    <string name="ungoogled_chromium__warning">- Ungoogled Chromium uses the technical foundation of Google Chrome and thus indirectly supports the monopoly position of the Chromium render engine.</string>
    <string name="unsupported_abi_dialog__message">The selected browser is incompatible with your smartphone\'s processor. Please select a different browser.</string>
    <string name="unsupported_abi_dialog__title">Unsupported device</string>
    <string name="update_interval__12h">12 hours</string>
    <string name="update_interval__15min">15 minutes</string>
    <string name="update_interval__18h">18 hours</string>
    <string name="update_interval__1d">1 day</string>
    <string name="update_interval__1h">1 hour</string>
    <string name="update_interval__1m">1 month</string>
    <string name="update_interval__1w">1 week</string>
    <string name="update_interval__2d">2 days</string>
    <string name="update_interval__2h">2 hours</string>
    <string name="update_interval__2w">2 weeks</string>
    <string name="update_interval__30min">30 minutes</string>
    <string name="update_interval__3d">3 days</string>
    <string name="update_interval__4d">4 days</string>
    <string name="update_interval__4h">4 hours</string>
    <string name="update_interval__5d">5 days</string>
    <string name="update_interval__6d">6 days</string>
    <string name="update_interval__6h">6 hours</string>
    <string name="update_interval__8h">8 hours</string>
    <string name="notification__update_available__channel_descr">Notification channel for available %1$s updates.</string>
    <string name="notification__update_available__channel_name">"%1$s" update notification</string>
    <string name="update_notification__text">Click to install update</string>
    <string name="update_notification__title">Update for %1$s available</string>
    <string name="vivaldi__description">Discover a blazingly fast Internet browser! Vivaldi is a new, free, and private web browser built with flexibility in mind. It comes packed with useful features including a built-in AdBlocker (pop-up blocker), tracking protection, and private translation. Browser options like proper desktop-style tabs, dark/light Themes, and layout choices help you make it yours.</string>
    <string name="vivaldi__title">Vivaldi Browser</string>
    <string name="vivaldi__warning">- Vivaldi is only partially open source.\n- It also uses the technical foundation of Google Chrome and thus indirectly supports the monopoly position of the Chromium render engine.</string>
    <string name="mull__title">Mull Browser</string>
    <string name="mull__description">This is a privacy oriented and deblobbed web browser based on Mozilla technology. It enables many features upstreamed by the Tor Uplift project using preferences from the arkenfox-user.js project. It is recommended to install \'uBlock Origin\'.</string>
    <string name="app_card__open_project_page">Open project page in browser</string>
    <string name="ungoogled_chromium__eol_reason">"The developer posted: \"I won't be able to update the versions for some time. If possible please use one of the browsers [that FFUpdater supports] in the meantime.\" https://github.com/ungoogled-software/ungoogled-chromium-android/issues/123"</string>
    <string name="tor_browser__title">Tor Browser</string>
    <string name="tor_browser__description">Tor Browser for Android is the only official mobile browser supported by the Tor Project, developers of the world’s strongest tool for privacy and freedom online.</string>
    <string name="orbot__description">Orbot is a free proxy app that empowers other apps to use the internet more securely. Orbot uses Tor to encrypt your Internet traffic and then hides it by bouncing through a series of computers around the world. Tor is free software and an open network that helps you defend against a form of network surveillance that threatens personal freedom and privacy, confidential business activities and relationships, and state security known as traffic analysis.</string>
    <string name="orbot__title">Orbot: Tor for Android</string>
    <string name="add_app_activity__label">Add New Application</string>
    <string name="crash_report_activity__label">Crash Reporter</string>
    <string name="add_app_activity__title_from_mozilla">From Mozilla</string>
    <string name="add_app_activity__title_good_privacy_browsers">Good Privacy Browsers</string>
    <string name="add_app_activity__title_better_than_google_chrome">Better than Google Chrome</string>
    <string name="add_app_activity__title_other_applications">Other Applications</string>
    <string name="add_app_activity__title_end_of_live_browser">End-of-life browser</string>
    <string name="add_app_activity__add_new_application">Add new application</string>
    <string name="settings__network__trust_user_cas__summary">Enable if data traffic should be inspected and altered by other apps. If you unsure, keep this option disabled.</string>
    <string name="settings__network__trust_user_cas__title">Trust user-added CAs</string>
    <string name="chromium__title">Chromium</string>
    <string name="chromium__description">Chromium is an open-source browser project that aims to build a safer, faster, and more stable way for all users to experience the web. This site contains design documents, architecture overviews, testing information, and more to help you learn to build and work with the Chromium source code.</string>
    <string name="chromium__warning">- Chromium uses the technical foundation of Google Chrome and thus indirectly supports the monopoly position of the Chromium render engine.</string>
    <string name="settings__background__update_check__when_device_idle__title">Update checks only if the device is idle</string>
    <string name="settings__background__update_check__when_device_idle__summary">Enable this if you do not want your applications being restarted by an background update. Disable this if you want a more predictable schedule for background update checks.</string>
    <string name="settings__background__update_check__when_device_idle__unsupported">This option is only available on Android Marshmallow or later.</string>
    <string name="mulch__title">Mulch</string>
    <string name="mulch__description">This is a security oriented and hardened web browser based on Chromium technology. Many anti-features are disabled/removed and a handful security features are enabled/added thanks to patches from the Vanadium project. The source repo also includes prebuilts and makefiles to allow other operating systems to include Mulch as their system WebView.</string>
    <string name="mulch__warning">- Mulch uses the technical foundation of Google Chrome and thus indirectly supports the monopoly position of the Chromium render engine.</string>
    <string name="fennecfdroid__title">Fennec F-Droid</string>
    <string name="fennecfdroid__description">Fennec F-Droid is based on the latest Firefox release (codenamed Fenix). It has proprietary bits and telemetry removed, but still connects to various Mozilla and Google services that can track users.</string>
    <string name="fennecfdroid__warning">FFUpdater downloads the files from the F-Droid servers and is therefore not faster.</string>
    <string name="network__dns_provider__title">DNS settings</string>
    <string name="network__custom_doh_server__dialog_message">Enter the connection details for the custom DoH server in one of these formats:\n\nurl;ip1\n\nurl;ip1;ip2\n\nurl;ip1;ip2;ip3\n\nurl;ip1;ip2;ip3;ip4\n\nFor example: https://dns.google/dns-query;8.8.8.8 or https://dns.quad9.net/dns-query;2620:fe::fe;2620:fe::9</string>
    <string name="network__custom_doh_server__title">Custom DNS over HTTPS server</string>
    <string name="network__proxy__dialog_message">If you want to use a SOCKS or HTTP proxy, enter the connection details here. Use one of these formats:\n\nSOCKS/HTTP;ip/domain;port\n\nSOCKS/HTTP;ip/domain;port;username;password\n\nFor example: SOCKS;1.2.3.4;22 or HTTP;5.6.7.8;80;user1;pw123 or HTTP;p.webshare.io;80;u;p. Leave it empty if you want to use the system proxy configuration.\n\nLimitation: If you change \'DNS settings\' in the settings to a DNS over HTTPS server, you have to enter the domain of the proxy server. IPs will not work.</string>
    <string name="network__proxy__title">Proxy</string>
    <string name="settings__network_category__title">Network</string>
    <string name="settings__device_category__title">Device</string>
    <string name="device__prefer_32bit_apks__summary">Enable if your device is usually low on memory. FFUpdater will then use 32-bit APKs which usually require less memory.</string>
    <string name="device__prefer_32bit_apks__title">Prefer 32-Bit APKs</string>
    <string name="installer__method__root_not_granted">Root permission not granted!</string>
    <string name="installer__method__shizuku_not_installed">Shizuku is not installed!</string>
    <string name="network__dns_provider__system">Use system DNS</string>
    <string name="network__dns_provider__digital_society_ch">DNS over HTTPS: Digital Society Switzerland</string>
    <string name="network__dns_provider__quad9">DNS over HTTPS: Quad9</string>
    <string name="network__dns_provider__cloudflare">DNS over HTTPS: Cloudflare</string>
    <string name="network__dns_provider__google">DNS over HTTPS: Google</string>
    <string name="network__dns_provider__custom">Custom DNS over HTTPS server</string>
    <string name="network__dns_provider__no">No DNS (just for testing)</string>
    <string name="installer__method__session">Session installer: Recommended for most devices. On Android 12 or above, apps can be updated silently after one user confirmation.</string>
    <string name="installer__method__native">Native installer: Fallback if the session installer does not work on your smartphone.</string>
    <string name="installer__method__root">Root installer: Update apps without a confirmation dialog. This requires a rooted smartphone.</string>
    <string name="installer__method__shizuku">Shizuku installer: Update apps without a confirmation dialog. This requires the Shizuku app or the Sui Magisk module.</string>
    <string name="background__separate_notification_channels__summary">Use different notification channels for each individual app</string>
    <string name="background__separate_notification_channels__title">Different notification channels</string>
    <string name="notification__update_available__generic_channel_name">App update notification</string>
    <string name="notification__update_available__generic_channel_descr">Notification channel for available app updates.</string>
    <string name="notification__install_error__generic_channel_descr">Notification channel for failed app updates.</string>
    <string name="notification__install_error__generic_channel_name">App update failure notification</string>
    <string name="notification__network_error__title">Network error in background job</string>
    <string name="notification__network_error__text">This error should occur only rarely. However, if it occurs frequently, you should report it. Click here to view the detailed error message.</string>
    <string name="tor_browser_alpha__title">Tor Browser Alpha</string>
    <string name="tor_browser_alpha__description">Tor Browser is the only official mobile browser supported by the Tor Project, developers of the world’s strongest tool for privacy and freedom online.\n\nTor Browser will ALWAYS be free, but donations make it possible. The Tor Project is a 501©(3) nonprofit based in the US. Please consider making a contribution today. Every gift makes a difference: https://donate.torproject.org.\n\nLearn how to report bugs and provide feedback at https://support.torproject.org/misc/bug-or-feedback/!</string>
    <string name="generic_app_warning__beta_version">- This app is designed for developers and testers. It may contain various bugs that can affect your usual work with the browser.</string>
    <string name="main_activity__app_was_signed_by_different_certificate">This app was signed with a different certificate and can\'t be updated with FFUpdater.</string>
    <string name="foreground__hide_apps_signed_by_different_certificate__title">Hide apps that are signed by a different certificate.</string>
    <string name="firefox_focus_beta__title">Firefox Focus Beta</string>
    <string name="firefox_focus_beta__description">Use Firefox Focus for everything you want to keep separate from your main browser — for all those get in get out and forget about it moments. No tabs, no fuss, no muss. Block online trackers too. One tap, and your browsing history is completely destroyed.\n\nFirefox Focus is the perfect get in/get out, search and destroy, I’m on a mission that’s none-of-your-business — web browser.</string>
    <string name="duckduckgo_android__title">DuckDuckGo Private Browser</string>
    <string name="duckduckgo_android__description">The DuckDuckGo app provides the most comprehensive online privacy protection with the push of a button. With one download, you get a new everyday browser that offers seamless protection while you search and browse, and access to tracking protections for emails you receive and apps you use. Many of these protections are not offered in most popular browsers by default.</string>
    <string name="duckduckgo_android__warning">- DuckDuckGo uses the system webview to display websites.\n- There was a controversy about not blocking all cookies from Microsoft - but this has been fixed.</string>
    <string name="privacy_browser__title">Privacy Browser</string>
    <string name="privacy_browser__warning">FFUpdater downloads the files from the F-Droid servers and is therefore not faster.</string>
    <string name="privacy_browser__description">The only way to prevent data from being abused is to prevent it from being collected in the first place. Privacy Browser has two primary goals: Minimize the data that is sent to the internet and minimize the data that is stored on the device.</string>
    <string name="eol_reason__browser_no_longer_maintained">The browser is no longer maintained.</string>
    <string name="background__installation__when_screen_off__summary">Try to install updates only when the device screen is off.</string>
    <string name="background__installation__when_screen_off__title">Install only when screen off</string>
    <string name="notification__bg_update_check__unreliable_execution__channel_name">Background update check not executed</string>
    <string name="notification__bg_update_check__unreliable_execution__channel_description">Warning about unreliable execution of the background update check</string>
    <string name="notification__bg_update_check__unreliable_execution__title">Background update check is not executed reliably</string>
    <string name="notification__bg_update_check__unreliable_execution__text">Maybe it is caused by the battery or performance settings for your device. Click this notification to disable battery optimization for this app.</string>
    <string name="crash_report__report_is_copied_to_clipboard">Crash report is copied to your clipboard</string>
    <string name="installer__android_too_old_for_shizuku">Your Android is too old for Shizuku.</string>
    <string name="add_app_activity__title_based_on_firefox">Based on Firefox</string>
    <string name="add_app_activity__title_good_security_browsers">Good Security Browser</string>
    <string name="notification__uncaught_exception__channel_name">Crash notifications</string>
    <string name="notification__uncaught_exception__channel_description">Unexpected errors which crash FFUpdater.</string>
    <string name="notification__uncaught_exception__title">FFUpdater crashed</string>
    <string name="notification__uncaught_exception__text">Click to view the error report.</string>
    <string name="notification__bachground_work__channel_name">Background Work Notifications</string>
    <string name="notification__bachground_work__channel_description">Notifications of the background work</string>
    <string name="notification__bachground_work__title">Executing background work</string>
    <string name="notification__bachground_work__text">This notification is required for a reliable execution. Depending on your settings, updates are fetched, downloaded and installed in the background. This notification can be hidden or muted without stopping the background work. After the check is completed, the notification will is also be closed.</string>
    <string name="notification__bachground_work__action_title">Cancel this background work</string>
    <string name="mulch_wv__title">Mulch System WebView</string>
    <string name="mulch_wv__description">This is a security oriented and hardened system WebView based on Chromium technology. Many anti-features are disabled/removed and a handful security features are enabled/added thanks to patches from the Vanadium project.</string>
    <string name="app_installer__failed_to_validate_signature_of_download">Failed to validate the signature of the download.</string>
    <string name="app_installer__failed_to_verify_signature_of_installed_app">Failed to check installed app.</string>
    <string name="ffupdater__different_signature_message">This version of FFUpdater has been signed by F-Droid, so only F-Droid can distribute updates. To get updates faster, uninstall FFUpdater and install the developer signed version. With this version FFUpdater can update itself without waiting for F-Droid.</string>
    <string name="installer__method__title">Installer method</string>
    <string name="cromite__title">Cromite</string>
    <string name="cromite__description">Cromite is a Chromium fork based on Bromite with built-in support for ad blocking and an eye for privacy.</string>
    <string name="cromite__warning">- Cromite uses the technical foundation of Google Chrome and thus indirectly supports the monopoly position of the Chromium render engine.</string>
    <string name="main_activity__unexpected_error">Unexpected error occurred.</string>
    <string name="thorium__title">Thorium Browser for Android</string>
    <string name="thorium__description">The fastest browser on Earth. Chromium fork for Linux named after radioactive element No. 90.</string>
    <string name="thorium__warning">- Thorium uses the technical foundation of Google Chrome and thus indirectly supports the monopoly position of the Chromium render engine.</string>
    <string name="k9mail__title">K-9 Mail</string>
    <string name="k9mail__description">Full-featured email client</string>
    <string name="fairemail__title">FairEmail</string>
    <string name="fairmail__description">Fully featured, open source, privacy friendly email app for Android</string>
    <string name="cardview_dialog__self_description_label">Self description:</string>
    <string name="cardview_dialog__warnings_label">Warnings:</string>
    <string name="cardview_dialog__auto_bg_update">Automatic background update</string>
    <string name="cardview_dialog__exit">Close</string>
    <string name="app_install_info_dialog__install">Install</string>
    <string name="cardview_dialog__install">Install latest version</string>
</resources>